smashmuck.com 2016-05-07

# Kiz Studios

At Kiz Studios (Kiz), we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of your information. You may access our products on a Kiz website or by way of other websites such as an App Store. Our products consist of games and activities for general audiences. 

Our Policy Regarding Children

Kiz online or mobile products and services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. When a Kiz online or mobile product or service does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, the product or service will either block such users from the site, or will ensure that personal information is not collected from the child. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal information to us. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any personal information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at privacy@kizstudios.com. 

APP Sites

As the Developer of Apps on several platforms (including Apple’s iTunes, Amazon’s Market Place and Google Play), 

Kiz 1) allows players of some Apps to send emails to their friends with images they create in-app, although Kiz does not collect or use those email addresses; 

2) allows access to links to third party social media; 

3) displays advertising within Apps; and 

4) provide in-App purchase functionality. Kiz does not collect or use any PII from those activities. UDIDs and geolocation information are available to Kiz as the developer; UDIDs and geolocation information collection is a function of the development process created by the Publishers (Apple, Amazon, etc) but Kiz does not collect or share that information; 

5) Has access to anonymous device identifiers; 

6) Utilizes analytic third party tools. 

Types of Personal Information Collected 

We may collect your email address for the purpose of signing up to an Account or Newsletter. Where information may be received in email communications to our customer service site, we will protect those communications from any other use. 

Kiz online activities may include surveys or sweepstakes or contests; we may ask you to provide contact information or your preferences. Polls and surveys are conducted to find better ways of serving your needs. Kiz will not request more personal information than is reasonably necessary at any collection point. 

When visitors come to our site, we passively collect certain computer information. We collect and then generate and store logs indicating Kiz website usage statistics. Collected information may include the type of computer operating system, the web browser, and IP address, and the frequency with which guests visit various parts of our sites. We do this to make our sites more interesting and useful to you and for various purposes related to our business. We may collect this information through the use of software technologies such as unique identifiers, or "cookies." 

Within your computer settings, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you may not have access to some features that make your Web experience smoother, and some of our services may not function properly.

Does Kiz share information about me with others?

We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site so that our partners may also understand how often people use their services and our service. 

If we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer PII to a third party as part of that transaction, to the extent permitted by applicable law. 

Please note that your access to and the ability to play any Kiz game may be subject to certain third party terms and conditions and privacy policies, including but not limited to application stores, mobile software platforms, on-line gaming platforms and payment providers. 

What does Kiz do with the information we collect?

To provide customer support services, and to verify any claims or requests you make. 

To enforce our terms and conditions, and prevent or detect hacking activities, security breaches or safety risks in connection with our websites. 

To send service announcements and messages if you request such information. 

To send you email newsletters about our games, including new game features, if you have requested such information. 

To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our websites. We may share this anonymous information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

For our own internal marketing and demographic studies and to help us improve our websites. 

In the event of an actual or proposed (including as part of negotiations for any) merger, or business combination or sale of substantially all of our assets or a business operation to which such information relates, or as provided under bankruptcy or applicable insolvency laws or by the enforcement of equitable rights. 

To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government, regulatory or law enforcement authority, to protect or assist in protecting our users, systems or the public, or to otherwise enforce legal rights as determined in our sole and absolute discretion. 

Ad Serving Technology

Kiz websites, online or mobile products or services may employ proprietary or third party ad serving technologies that use cookies, clear GIFs, web beacons, tracking pixels or other technologies to collect information as a result of ad serving through our products or services as well as to help track results.  Some dynamic in-game advertisement serving technologies enable advertising to be temporarily uploaded into your game, web browser or mobile device and replaced while you are online.  We or third parties operating the advertisement serving technology may use information such as age and gender as well as information logged from your hardware or device to ensure that appropriate advertising is presented within the site, online or mobile product or service and to calculate or control the number of unique and repeat views of a given ad, and/or deliver ads that relate to your interests and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns.   We or third parties may collect data for this purpose including IP address, geographic location, device ID's, information about your software, applications and hardware, browser information (and/or information passed via your browser), hardware, machine or device make and model, advertisement(s) served, in game location, length of time an advertisement was visible, other Internet and website usage information, web pages and mobile internet sites which have been viewed by you (as well as date and time), domain type, size of the advertisement, advertisement response (if any), and angle of view.  The data described here may be used and disclosed in accordance with the privacy policy of the company providing the ad serving technology.

The advertising companies who deliver ads for us may combine the information collected or obtained from Kiz with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your web browser's activities across their network of websites. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

Analytic Metrics Tools and Other Technologies

Kiz also uses third party analytics technologies to collect information when you use our online products and services and/or play our games on your PC or mobile device. These tools and technologies use server log files, web beacons, cookies, tracking pixels and other technologies to collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses (including for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location), mobile or other hardware device ID or other device identifiers, browser types, browser language, information passed from your browser (if any), referring and exit pages, and URLs, platform type, click information, information about your media, peripheral hardware, software and/or applications installed on your machine and/or device, domain names and types, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, advertising conversion rates, the date and amount of time spent on particular pages, other Internet and website usage information, game state and the date and time of activity on our websites or games, information about how your game is used, including game metrics and statistics, feature usage and purchase history, as well as unique hardware identifiers such as MAC Address, mobile unique device ID (if applicable) and other similar information. 

The third party analytics companies who collect information on our sites and in the context of our online and mobile products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies. 

Our policy regarding children

Kiz online or mobile products and services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. When a Kiz online or mobile product or service does collect age information, and users identify themselves as under 13, the product or service will prevent personal information from being collected from the child.

No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal information to us. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any personal information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at  [privacy@kizstudios.com](mailto:privacy@kizstudios.com)

Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information available to us online. We use Secure Sockets Layer technology to protect data during transmission, and adopt careful internal procedures to safeguard this information in our system. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

Do Not Track

While your browser may allow you to implement a "Do Not Track" ("DNT") feature through your browser's settings, our Sites are not configured to honor DNT signals at this time.

How can I access my information and change the information collected and retained?

Please contact [privacy@kizstudios.com](mailto:privacy@kizstudios.com) to access any personal information we collect online from you to correct factual errors, to request to have this information deleted or to request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

How can you contact us?

Kiz Studios  
327 Dahlonega St. Building 1200   
Cumming, GA 30040 

phone: 1.888.549.8691  
Email: [privacy@kizstudios.com](mailto:privacy@kizstudios.com)

Learn more about online safety

The Internet offers a world of opportunity for kids. [OnGuard Online.gov __](http://onguardonline.gov/)is a great place to find out everything you need to know about online and mobile safety.  For the younger people in your life, the [NetCetera toolkit](http://onguardonline.gov/netcetera) is a terrific resource to help kids handle bullying, guard personal information, and stay safe while exploring the Internet.  In addition, [Living Life Online](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/microsites/livinglifeonline/index.shtm) is _the_  resource for young people to learn how to make smart choices online.

Effective Date

The privacy policy set out above is effective as of March 14, 2014. We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at our sole discretion. Changes to this privacy policy will be clearly marked.
